While reading the diary of Emperor Rosel,
Klein was deeply moved by the simplified Chinese characters
and the identity of the fellow-time traveler.
In the diary, Emperor Rosel recorded crucial information
about potions, such as digestion and role-playing,
which were invaluable to Klein.
He yearned to find more diaries
to unlock the secrets of the mysterious realm.
During a conversation with Old Neil,
Klein learned about the rarity of extraordinary events
and the preciousness of Rosel's diaries.
The two also humorously discussed the idea
of establishing a society for the protection
of magical creatures, easing the tense atmosphere.
While collecting weapons and equipment,
Klein had a light-hearted exchange with Old Neil
but couldn't shake his fixation
on the contents of Rosel's diaries.
He regretted not asking more about sequences and potions,
but found new hope in his exploration journey
with the newly acquainted Night Watchman, Leonard Mitchell.
Klein returned to the reception hall,
where Rosel informed him that the captain asked him
to come back on Monday to handle personal matters first.
Grateful for this humane management,
Klein originally planned to inform the University of Tingen
that he would not attend the interview,
but now could leisurely go.
He inquired about the starting sequence controlled
by the church, and Rosel was surprised
if he wanted to become an extraordinary being,
warning of the dangers.
Klein explained he just wanted to understand common knowledge,
and Ros, whose father was once a Night Watchman, became excited,
but eventually revealed that the church's
starting sequence was sleepless, sequence nine.
Klein learned that Captain Dunne was sequence seven nightmare,
one of only two in Tingen City.
Ros also mentioned other sequences like Seer and Medium,
and Klein was interested in Seer
as it aligned with his desire to explore mysterious knowledge.
Finally, Klein decided to treat his sister to a good meal
with his newly earned 12 pounds.
Walking along Zotter Street,
Klein, with only three pence left,
decided to buy a cane to make change
for the four pence public carriage fare.
He entered the Virkel hats and cloak shop
and chose a moderately priced water soaked wood cane.
When paying, he tried to haggle but failed,
eventually leaving satisfied with his purchase.
Back at the apartment,
he practiced using the cane and revolver,
enhancing his sense of security.
When Melissa returned home,
Klein suggested going out to celebrate his new job,
despite Melissa's concerns about moving
and increased expenses.
Klein insisted on the start of a new life.
Klein and Melissa discussed moving matters,
with Klein emphasizing decorum and social rules
while Melissa cared about thrift in the future.
Klein eventually convinced Melissa,
planning to move to a townhouse with a private washroom
and mentioning waiting for Benson to return before acting.
Melissa mentioned her classmate Selena's brother
post-poning marriage for a stable life,
while Klein assured her of his stable salary,
not needing to worry excessively.
Then, Klein suggested a celebration,
and Melissa agreed but emphasized the need for thrift.
Klein bought ingredients and gave Melissa extra money
for fruit and lemon cake,
showing his care for his sister.
Klein went to the University of Tingen
to handle the interview matters,
appreciating the university environment
and reminiscing about his rowing experience.
He informed in advance that he would not attend the interview,
as he had found a job,
receiving congratulations
from the faculty member Haven Stone.
He coincidentally met his mentor Kern
and the faculty member Azeek,
discussing job choices in the case of Welch,
with Azeek feeling familiar with antagonists,
but unable to recall details.
Azeek and Quentin Kern discussed historical issues
and Klein expressed interest in the history
of the fourth epoch, requesting information from them.
Kern was satisfied with Klein's performance,
and as a guest for Klein's address,
learning he was about to move,
Kern reminded Klein to improve his living environment.
Klein inquired about reports on Welch and Nia,
but due to the tight meeting time,
Azeek handed the newspaper to Klein and left.
Klein read the newspaper,
finding reports on the Welch case,
with the police having identified the suspect.
He felt a sense of being watched
and decided to seek help at the church of St. Selina.
Inside the church,
he contacted Dunsmith through the confessional,
reporting being followed.
Klein followed the middle-aged priest
through a dimly lit corridor,
passing through heavily guarded passages,
and entering underground stone steps.
The priest indicated that the left path
at the crossroads led to the Charnis Gate
and Klein responded with religious rituals.
He descended alone,
turning back to see the priest standing like a wax statue,
continuing to the crossroads
and returning to the Black Thorn Security Company
without turning towards the Charnis Gate.
In the reception hall, Klein spoke with Rose,
learning the captain's location.
He found Dunn and reported being followed.
Dunn speculated it could be a private detective
hired by Welch's father
or someone seeking the antigenous family notebook.
Dunn advised Klein to return the same way,
doing anything he wanted,
but not scaring off the follower or breaking the law.
Klein returned to the church,
seeing the middle-aged priest again,
then left the church,
feeling persistent surveillance.
He suspected the follower had a dark past,
fearing the church.
Klein went to the Zotter shooting club
to practice his marksmanship,
enhancing his self-defense capabilities.
After practice, Klein returned home,
sharing the good news with his brother Benson.
He had found a new job
with a weekly salary of three pounds.
They decided to celebrate,
planning to buy ingredients together in the afternoon.
Klein expressed dissatisfaction
with the complex currency system
and Benson responded humorously, both laughing.
Benson seriously rebutted,
no not one of them,
and Klein understood after a pause,
both laughing again.
Benson added,
a reasonable and simple currency system
requires knowing numbers and the decimal system,
but there are two few such talents among the big wigs.
Klein and Benson had humorous interactions during dinner,
discussing the rental contract
and landlord Frank's intelligence.
Benson planned to visit the landlord
with Klein the next day to view the house.
After dinner,
Klein went to the market to buy ingredients,
feeling watched but not contacted.
Back home, he did simple exercises
and reviewed textbooks.
In the evening,
the three siblings enjoyed a hearty dinner
celebrating Klein's new job with a warm atmosphere.
After dinner, they cleaned up
and studied individually until late at night.
In his dream,
Klein received instructions from Captain Dunn
that someone had infiltrated his room.
Waking up,
he found a stranger searching through his things.
Klein's heart raced,
his body trembling,
momentarily losing focus.
The intruder's pause allowed him to regain his senses,
quickly reaching for the revolver under his pillow.
Klein's heartbeat accelerated,
facing the intruder,
he calmly grasped the revolver under his pillow,
aiming more to intimidate than to attack.
The intruder faced with the gun,
slowly turned around
and Klein remained calm,
guiding the intruder towards the door.
As the door half opened,
the intruder suddenly crouched and rolled,
the door slamming shut.
Then, the serene sound of poetry came,
allowing Benson and others to fall asleep again.
Klein realized his bullets were blanks
and patiently waited for the fight to end.
Soon, Dunn Smith announced the problem solved
and revealed the intruder was from the secret society
related to the Antigonus family notebook.
Dunn offered Klein the choice
to become an extraordinary being,
introducing three sequence nine options.
Seer, Corpse Collector, and Fortune Teller.
Klein showed interest in Seer and Fortune Teller,
especially the latter,
as Emperor Rozel had expressed regret about it.
Klein inquired about the abilities of Fortune Teller
and Dunn explained it involved astrology,
card divination, et cetera,
but lacked direct combat means.
Klein hesitated and Dunn advised him
to make a decision by Monday.
After returning home,
Klein's emotions settled,
reminiscing about the past
and eventually made his choice.
The next day, Klein discussed renting matters
with his family,
with Benson mentioning
the Tingen City Housing Improvement Company,
offering options for the lower middle class.
They went to the company,
where Scott greeted them
and introduced several unrented townhouses.
The siblings decided to view the house at Narcissus Street 2.
Narcissus Street 2, 4 and 6
were connected gray blue buildings,
with Mr. Scott leading Klein,
Benson and Melissa on a tour.
The living room was spacious,
the dining room connected to the living room,
the kitchen and washroom on the first floor,
and four bedrooms and two washrooms on the second floor.
Scott mentioned the rent and deposit
and Klein inquired about the purchase price,
learning it was 850 pounds,
feeling the pressure after mental calculations.
Benson successfully negotiated the rent to 12 shillings,
signing the contract and notarizing it.
The siblings returned to their old residents,
negotiating the least termination with Mr. Frank,
with Benson successfully convincing Frank
to accept compensation by citing rent increases
and finding new tenants.
Then, they bought formal wear and moved,
busy until evening.
The next day Klein dressed in new formal wear,
went to the Black Thorn Security Company,
discussing career choices with Captain Dunn,
ultimately deciding to become a fortune teller.
Dunn gazed at Klein, the silence conveying pressure,
but Klein firmly returned the gaze.
Dunn warned of the irreversible nature of potions,
and Klein responded with a smile,
respecting his inner choice,
firmly replying, fortune teller.
Dunn Smith and Klein exchanged glances,
a moment of silence followed,
and Dunn warned of the irreversible nature
of potion consumption.
Klein responded resolutely,
choosing the fortune teller, potion.
Dunn led him underground,
explaining the sources of mystical knowledge,
including exploration, divine blessings,
and dangerous whispers.
They reached the alchemy room,
where Dunn arranged for Old Neil to prepare the potion,
reminding Klein to be cautious.
Old Neil briefly described the potion preparation process,
emphasizing the precision of key ingredients.
Finally, Klein witnessed the birth of the fortune teller,
potion, feeling the mysterious gaze,
facing the deep blue viscous potion, Klein hesitated,
asking if a ritual or incantation was needed.
Old Neil humorously suggested a series
of relaxation activities,
eventually explaining these were just methods
to relieve tension.
Klein mustered his courage and drank the potion,
instantly feeling a cold, stimulating sensation,
his vision blurring, colors intensifying,
as if entering a world filled with light and illusions.
He realized he was still in place,
returning to normal through conscious descent,
but feeling his head swell and hearing mysterious whispers.
Old Neil guided him to control
the overflowing potion power through meditation,
and Klein successfully entered a meditative state,
feeling calm.
Old Neil then taught him clairvoyance
and Klein gradually mastered it,
seeing the aura colors of himself and Old Neil,
eventually discovering a pair of nearly illusory eyes
behind Old Neil, feeling dinging.
Old Neil demonstrated a ritual magic symbol
and Klein found it magical,
beginning to explore the alchemy room through clairvoyance.
He discovered that the materials of supernatural species
still had residual spirituality,
crucial for potion preparation.
Old Neil mentioned the root causes
of extraordinary beings losing control
and shared the formula for the corpse collector potion,
making Klein uncomfortable.
Klein wondered why he hadn't seen spirits,
and Old Neil explained that this was because
the headquarters of the Night Watch team
had many extraordinary beings,
not allowing spirits to wander.
Klein experienced eyebrow twitching and hallucinations,
and Old Neil explained this was a normal effect
of clairvoyance on new extraordinary beings,
teaching him how to exit the clairvoyance state.
After practice, Klein learned to open and close clairvoyance
by lightly tapping his eyebrows twice.
After overusing clairvoyance,
Klein felt extremely tired,
and Old Neil advised him to go home and rest.
After returning home, Klein slept,
waking up to check the time,
ensuring he hadn't missed the gathering
with the hanged man and justice.
He reviewed historical textbooks,
preparing for the gathering.
At the gathering time, he entered the temple
above the gray fog through a specific ritual
ready to communicate with the hanged man and justice.
In the dimly lit basement, Alaj Wilson gazed
at a mysterious black liquid in a bottle,
the liquid inside emitting the sound of waves
with fog writhing on the surface.
The time pointed to three,
and Alaj's eyes suddenly turned black,
deep red light then surged and gulfing him.
In the hall family's residence in Belkland,
Odelli locked her room door,
preparing to record the formula.
She eagerly looked at the mirror,
only to see deep red light erupt, swallowing her.
Above the gray fog in the temple,
deep red light gushed from both sides
of the bronze long table, forming two vague figures.
Odelli greeted Mr. Fool and Mr. Hangman
and Klein observed their auras,
finding that Mr. Hangman seemed to be
a powerful extraordinary being.
Odelli inquired about the reception of the ghost shark blood,
and Alaj thanked her,
preparing to inform her of the audience potion formula.
He emphasized the precautions for preparing the potion
and Odelli carefully recorded it.
Klein suddenly interjected,
proposing the concepts of digestion and role-playing,
deeply inspiring Alaj,
who considered it a precious hint.
Klein proposed a commission,
hoping to gather the secret diaries of Rozel Gustaf.
The secret diaries of Emperor Rozel
caught the attention of Mr. Fool.
Klein and Alaj discussed the interpretation of the diaries,
with Klein hinting that he might have a method of interpretation.
Odelli tried to imagine transferring the texts,
demonstrating Mr. Fool's mysterious abilities.
Klein explained the requirements of the audience potion,
emphasizing the importance of maintaining neutral observation.
Alaj shared news about the voyage of Admiral Ludwig,
while Klein revealed the secret society
losing the Antigonus family notebook,
sparking a discussion about the reaction
of the Church of the Goddess of Night.
Odelli shared practical tips
for social occasions and political pressure.
The entire exchange was filled with a mysterious
and information exchanging atmosphere.
Odelli discussed government chaos
and Klein proposed a civil service examination system.
Alaj mocked ministers as no better than baboons.
Klein explained the details of the examination,
and Odelli was surprised by the simplicity
and effectiveness of the plan.
The gathering ended,
and Klein pondered the issue of new members,
deciding to act cautiously.
He experienced the abilities of extraordinary beings,
contemplating the role of fortune teller.
Odelli recorded the potion formula,
planning to obtain the materials.
Alaj reflected on Mr. Fools' mystery.
Klein, under the scorching sun,
changed into plain clothes
and walked towards Welch's residence.
On the way, he recalled the circus trainer
and the Antigonus family notebook,
feeling heavy-hearted.
At the slin bakery, Mrs. Wynton's sweet iced tea
and casual chat lifted his spirits.
Continuing on, Klein felt the oppressive atmosphere
of the street, using clairvoyance
to discover the residence pessimistic emotions.
He decided to explore Welch's residence,
but found no notebook.
Then, he noticed the sign of the fortune telling club
and decided to explore it,
considering joining to enhance his fortune telling skills.
Klein arrived at the fortune telling club,
inquiring about fortune telling matters.
The receptionist introduced several members,
including the expensive hains and the beginner graces.
Klein chose graces,
despite the receptionist's reminder that he was a beginner.
Klein insisted,
and the two had a fortune telling session,
with graces offering a free exchange,
but Klein insisted on paying.
The fortune telling results showed
that the item Klein sought might not have been found by others.
Klein also noticed,
graces might have health issues
and advised him to see a doctor.
Leaving the club, Klein planned to join it
to better play the role of,
fortune teller.
He then went to the Black Thorn Security Company,
discussing the mystery of the antagonist family notebook
with Leonard.
Klein and Leonard discussed the possible fate of the notebook,
with Klein speculating it might be hidden
to prepare for future sacrifices,
while Leonard suggested it might be destroyed
to cover up evil.
Klein expressed dissatisfaction with Leonard's suspicions,
but Leonard shifted the topic,
asking about Klein's findings,
who said there were no new discoveries
and plan to change routes.
Klein went to the armory to collect bullets,
encountering rows and blight,
with rows curious about Klein becoming an extraordinary being,
and blight expressing awe for extraordinary beings.
Klein collected bullets and left with rows,
practicing shooting and physical training.
Back home, Klein discussed family finances with Melissa,
successfully convincing her to take public carriages
to save time for studying.
The next day,
Klein and Benson went to work separately,
with Klein encountering old Neil and rows at the company,
starting new mystical studies,
with old Neil teaching an interesting technique.
Klein was curious about Old Neil's mystical technique,
and Old Neil asked him to make two cups of coffee,
one with something bad.
Klein did so, adding sole dirt to one cup.
Old Neil used divination to confirm which cup was problematic,
and explained the principles of divination.
Klein became deeply interested in divination techniques,
deciding to apply for the purchase of divination tools.
Old Neil then began teaching Klein the basics of mystical studies,
including symbols and constellations.
After the lesson, Old Neil advised Klein
to practice more and meditate,
supporting his decision to join the Fortune Telling Club
to enhance his divination skills.
Klein decided to apply for the fees to join the club,
to better monitor potential cultists.
Finally, Old Neil expressed dissatisfaction
with the dirt Klein added to the coffee,
demanding he handle it immediately.